

Farhad Ali

Front End Developer



Professional Summary

I am a professional Front End Developer with 2+years of experience. My Core Skills are HTML CSS JavaScript WordPress React jQuery Angular Js bootstrap Tailwind Css etc. I am always ready to get Good position where I can Use my Core Skills 100%



Work History

2021-07 -Current

Freelancer

Web Developer

2022-04 -2022-05

Web Developer Intern

Internship

https://www.thesparksfoundationsingapore.org/joinus/internship-positions/

2021-03 -2021-04

Web Development Intern

Internship

interns.pk

প্রি

Education

2018-10 -2022-10

Bechlors : Information Technology

Quest Nawabshah

2015-05 -2017-05

Intermediate

SI Degree Government College Hala New

2013-04 -

Matriculation

2015-04

MG Government High School Hala New





Address

Hala New, Sindh, 70120

Phone

+923013590799

E-mall

farhadalimemon45@gmail.c om

Linkedin

https://www.linkedin.com/in /farhad-ali-memon-b1588

www

https://farhadali45.github.io/ portfolio.github.io/



HTML

Excellent

CSS

•••• Excellent

JavaScript

Very Good

Bootstrap

Excellent

Tailwind Css

Excellent

React

Very Good

JQuery

Verv Good

Angular Js

